<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Business News Aggregator</title>
  <description>Regulatory and business updates from various government sources</description>
  <link>https://[your-username].github.io/business-news-aggregator/</link>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  
  <item>
    <title>Regulatory Resolution: TechCorp Inc. Compliance Matter</title>
    <description>Federal regulators announced the resolution of a compliance matter involving TechCorp Inc. related to disclosure practices. The company has agreed to enhanced oversight procedures and will pay a settlement of $3.2 million to resolve the matter without admitting wrongdoing.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <link>https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2025-demo</link>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>DataFlow Systems Settles Disclosure Investigation</title>
    <description>Regulatory authorities have concluded their investigation into DataFlow Systems Inc. regarding information security disclosure practices. The company will implement additional compliance measures and pay $1.8 million to settle the investigation. The resolution covers disclosure procedures related to data security incidents.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <link>https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2025-demo-2</link>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Manufacturing Corp Resolves Export Control Review</title>
    <description>A leading manufacturing company has reached resolution with trade regulators regarding export control procedures. The review focused on documentation and reporting practices for international sales. Terms include process improvements and a compliance enhancement payment of $850,000.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <link>https://www.bis.doc.gov/news/2025-demo</link>
  </item>
    <item>
        <title>Whatever Company - Regulatory Resolution</title>
        <description>Compliance matter involving securities fraud. Settlement: 1m $. Details under review.</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:22:55 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>enforcement-1756383775950</guid>
        <category>enforcement</category>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Whatever Company - Regulatory Resolution</title>
        <description>Compliance matter involving securities fraud. Settlement: 1m $. Whatever company did something bad</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:57:41 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>enforcement-1756479461643</guid>
        <category>enforcement</category>
    </item>

        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Demo Regulatory Announcement]]></title>
            <link>https://example.com/demo/demo-1758045552106</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">demo-1758045552106</guid>
            <description><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE
For Immediate Release
Financial Regulatory Commission
September 15, 2023

SEC Announces $12.5 Million Penalty Against TechNova Solutions for Compliance Violations

Washington, D.C. - The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has levied a $12.5 million enforcement action against TechNova Solutions Inc. for systematic failures in financial reporting and internal control mechanisms.

Key Details:
- Violation Type: Material misstatement of financial controls
- Period of Investigation: 2020-2022
- Specific Findings: Inadequate risk management and non-transparent accounting practices

The enforcement action stems from a comprehensive audit revealing multiple instances of non-compliance with Sarbanes-Oxley Act reporting requirements. TechNova must implement comprehensive remediation measures, including:

1. Independent third-party compliance audit
2. Enhanced internal control infrastructure
3. Mandatory executive compliance training
4. Quarterly reporting to SEC oversight committee

&quot;These actions demonstrate our commitment to maintaining market integrity and protecting investor interests,&quot; said Elena Rodriguez, SEC Enforcement Division Director.

TechNova&#39;s stock price declined 4.3% following the announcement, reflecting market sensitivity to regulatory actions.

The company has 30 days to contest the findings or implement the prescribed corrective measures.

###

Contact:
SEC Media Relations
press@sec.gov
(202) 555-4321]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:59:12 GMT</pubDate>
            <category>Regulatory</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
