<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Business News Aggregator</title>
  <description>Regulatory and business updates from various government sources</description>
  <link>https://[your-username].github.io/business-news-aggregator/</link>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Demo Regulatory Announcement]]></title>
            <link>https://example.com/demo/demo-1760475878860</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">demo-1760475878860</guid>
            <description><![CDATA[Company Announcement
Eureka Inc of Pomona, CA (10/6/2025) is recalling Durra Ground Cinnamon 100 gram plastic container because it has the potential to be contaminated with lead.

Short term exposures to very low levels of lead may not elicit any symptoms. It is possible that increased blood lead levels may be the only apparent sign of lead exposure. Exposure to extremely high amounts of lead may result in overt and possibly severe symptoms for which an individual is likely to seek medical attention. While lead can affect nearly every bodily system, its effects depend upon the amount and duration of lead exposure and age/body weight.

If a child is exposed to enough lead for a protracted period of time (e.g., weeks to months) permanent damage to the central nervous system may occur. This can result in learning disorders, developmental defects, and other long-term health problems.

For adults, acute lead poisoning may cause a wide range of symptoms, including abdominal pain, muscle weakness, nausea, vomiting, diarrhea, weight loss, and bloody or decreased urinary output. Chronic lead exposure is associated with kidney dysfunction, hypertension, and neurocognitive effects. Lead can cause serious health problems if too much is ingested, such as damage to the brain and kidneys and can interfere with the production of red blood cells that carry oxygen to all parts of your body.

The affected product is packaged in Clear Plastic Container, 100G, Durra Brand, Cinnamon, UPC 6251136 034139 and has the affected Lot code: Batch No.: 06 B:02, Best by date: May 2026.

Product was distributed by Eureka Inc and sold at grocery stores in California and Michigan from 08/24/2024 to 10/6/2025.

No illnesses have been reported to date.

The recall was initiated after the FDA collected product samples and detected elevated levels of lead. The firm’s investigation is ongoing, including testing raw materials used in manufacturing the product.

Lead poisoning can be diagnosed through clinical testing, and individuals who have consumed affected product should talk to their health care providers about testing. Consumers who have purchased Brand Durra Brand Cinnamon are urged to return it to the place of purchase for a full refund. Consumers with questions may contact the company at 1-951-444-7779 from 10am - 5pm PST, 5 days a week, and PST.

This recall is being made with the knowledge of the U.S. Food and Drug Administration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 21:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
            <category>Regulatory</category>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Demo Regulatory Announcement]]></title>
            <link>https://example.com/demo/demo-1760560405044</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">demo-1760560405044</guid>
            <description><![CDATA[Summary
Company Announcement Date:
August 26, 2025
FDA Publish Date:
August 26, 2025
Product Type:
Food &amp; Beverages
Allergens
Reason for Announcement:
Undeclared Allergen – Sesame and Soy
Company Name:
Taylor Fresh Foods
Brand Name:
Taylor Farms
Product Description:
Honey Balsamic Salad Kit
Company Announcement
Salinas, Calif., August 26, 2025 – In response to a recall initiated by Latitude 36 Foods, LLC., Taylor Fresh Foods is voluntarily recalling the Taylor Farms Honey Balsamic Salad Kit 6/8.3oz. because it may contain undeclared sesame and soy allergens. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to sesame and soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.

Master packs — individual packets of dressing and toppings supplied by Latitude 36 Foods and included in Taylor Farms salad kits — incorrectly included Asian Sesame Ginger dressing rather than the intended Honey Balsamic Vinaigrette dressing, leading to the possibility of undeclared sesame and soy allergens in some Taylor Farms Honey Balsamic Salad Kits.

The Taylor Farms Honey Balsamic Salad Kit 6/8.3oz in scope of this recall was distributed in AL, AZ, CA, CO, DE, FL, GA, IN, KS, KY, LA, MI, MO, MS, NJ, NY, OH, OR, PA, TN, TX, UT, VA, WA and WV and has code dates starting with “TFRS” and “Best If Used By” date up to and including September 4, 2025. The product code can be found in the upper right-hand corner of the packaging.

Consumers who have the recalled salad kit should discard it immediately and not consume it. Refunds are available at the location of purchase. There have been no illnesses reported to Taylor Farms in connection with the recalled product. This recall does not apply to any other Taylor Farms products or brands. Consumers with any questions may contact our customer care team at 855-455-0098 Monday through Friday from 8am-5pm PT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:33:25 GMT</pubDate>
            <category>Regulatory</category>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Demo Regulatory Announcement]]></title>
            <link>https://example.com/demo/demo-1760561133344</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">demo-1760561133344</guid>
            <description><![CDATA[United States Securities and Exchange Commission
Washington, D.C.

The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) today announced a civil enforcement action against NexusTech Innovations, Inc. for multiple violations of securities disclosure regulations and financial reporting standards. After a comprehensive investigation spanning 18 months, the SEC has determined that NexusTech systematically misrepresented its financial performance between 2021 and 2022, artificially inflating revenue projections and concealing material weaknesses in internal accounting controls.

The enforcement action results in a $12.5 million monetary penalty against NexusTech, with $8.3 million to be paid directly to the U.S. Treasury and $4.2 million allocated for investor restitution. Additionally, the company&#x27;s Chief Financial Officer, Marcus Reiner, has been permanently barred from serving as an officer or director of a publicly traded company. The SEC&#x27;s findings revealed that Reiner knowingly authorized the submission of false quarterly reports that overstated the company&#x27;s cloud computing service revenue by approximately 37% during the specified period.

As part of the settlement, NexusTech must engage an independent third-party auditor to review and validate its financial reporting processes for the next three consecutive fiscal years. The company must also implement comprehensive compliance training for all senior financial personnel and establish enhanced internal control mechanisms to prevent future reporting irregularities. The SEC emphasizes that this action demonstrates its ongoing commitment to protecting investor interests and maintaining the integrity of public financial markets.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:45:33 GMT</pubDate>
            <category>Regulatory</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
